https://www.blackbottle.com/privacy-policy/

PRIVACY POLICY
INTRODUCTIONAll references to “our”, “us”, “we” or “company” within this policy and within the opt-in notice are deemed to refer to Distell Group Ltd, its subsidiaries, affiliates and associates.We endeavour to protect your personal privacy. We provide this Privacy Policy to help you to understand what we may do with any personal information that we obtain from you. By providing your personal information to us, you signify your acceptance of our policy and agree that we may collect, use and disclose your personal information as described in this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not provide your personal details to us. This policy is incorporated into, and part of, the Terms & Conditions, which govern your use of the site in general. We will use your information only for the purposes set out below.We may need to update this policy from time to time and recommend that you regularly check this page to ensure that you have read the most recent version.LEGAL PURCHASE AGEYou must not provide us with your personal information if you are not of legal age to purchase alcohol in the jurisdiction in which you reside and (if different) in the jurisdiction in which you are accessing the site. We do not intend to collect personal information from any individuals under the legal purchase age or market alcoholic beverages to anyone under the legal purchase age. If we receive notice or believe that someone under the legal purchase age has provided us with personal information we will make every reasonable effort to remove such personal information from our files or flag such personal information and retain it for the sole purpose of ensuring that it is not used any further.WHAT IS PERSONAL INFORMATION?Personal information is information about an identifiable individual, as defined by applicable law. It does not include aggregated information that does not allow you to be identified, nor does it include business contact information such as your name, title, business address and business phone number.COLLECTION AND USE OF YOUR PERSONAL DATAWhen you use this website, you may provide us with personal data, for example by completing online forms, online applications, or online order forms. We will only use your personal data for the purposes of dealing with your enquiry, the administration of any orders, the provision of any goods or services we offer, the administration of any account or membership held by you, answering questions or complaints you may have in relation to our goods or services, for internal marketing analysis, or (if you agree) to provide you with details of any new or improved products or services we may be offering from time to time (and you will be entitled to opt-out of any such communications at any time). We may also contact you at a later date to seek your consent to use of your personal data for different purposes. We will only use your personal data for the purpose of which you provided it, or for any other purpose that you expressly consent to. We may also collect personal data by using “cookies”. For more information about cookies visit our cookies page or www.allaboutcookies.org for assistance with adjusting your browser settings. We do not use any other web tracking software, web bugs or similar.SHARING YOUR PERSONAL DATAWe will not disclose any personal data which is provided by you through our website to any third party without your permission, other than (i) to any sub-contractors or agents engaged by us to provide any support or administration, facilities management or similar services (subject to such sub-contractors and/or agents undertaking to keep such personal data confidential); (ii) to any company or organisation to which we transfer our responsibilities to provide the goods or services to you; or (iii) where required by law or made in connection with legal or regulatory proceedings. We will not transfer your personal data outwith the European Economic Area (“EEA”) without your prior consent. If we do transfer your personal data outwith the EEA, we will use reasonable endeavours to assess the adequacy or the protections afforded in respect of personal data under the laws of the particular country concerned.SECURITYWe will not hold your personal data for any longer than is reasonable for the above purposes. We have taken reasonable precautions to keep your personal information secure. However you should be aware that any personal data submitted by you via the internet is at your own risk.UNSUBSCRIBE, ACCESS, QUESTIONS AND FURTHER INFORMATIONAt your request, where the law requires us to do so, we will confirm what personal information we hold about you, update your information, remove your information and/or correct any inaccuracies in such personal information if you contact us using the unsubscribe details provided below.If you would like to unsubscribe from communications about Distell Group Ltd, or if you have any privacy-related questions, concerns or complaints, please contact data.privacy@distellinternational.com.LINKSThis site may contain links or references to other websites outside of our control. Please be aware that we have no control over these sites and our privacy statement does not apply to these sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements and terms and conditions of linked or referenced sites you enter.As required, this policy will be supplemented by additional legal requirements in jurisdictions where we conduct business. Nothing in this policy or otherwise will create, or add to, any right or claim (whether legal, equitable or otherwise) that any individual or person may have at law or otherwise against the company or any third party or any of their respective directors, officers, employees, agents or representatives, nor will the existence of this policy or its application impose or add to any obligations or liability upon the company that the company does not already otherwise have under law.Distell Group Ltd is the owner of the Black Bottle brand and is therefore the data controller for this website. Distell owns several well-known brands in the alcoholic drinks sector and distributes all over the world.The company is registered in Scotland with headquarters at:8 Milton RoadCollege Milton NorthEast KilbrideG74 5BUScotlandRegistered No: SC109881https://www.distell.co.za/home/If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, please contact data.privacy@distellinternational.comTo contact us please use the phone numbers below:Tel: +44(0)1355 260999Fax: +44(0)1355 264355
Terms and Conditions | Privacy Policy | Modern Slavery Statement | Cookie Policy
